shockya.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Shockya.com. All references to ‘our’, ‘us’, ‘we’ or ‘company’ within this policy and within the opt-in notice are deemed to refer to Shockya.com , its subsidiaries, affiliates, parent companies and any of their related businesses.

We strive to protect your personal privacy. We provide this statement to help our readers understand what we may do with any and all information that we obtain from you (including but not limited to personal information, comments and blog posts). By providing your personal details to us, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to this statement, please do not provide the information or details to us. 

**Collecting Personal Information**

You may choose to provide us with personal information if, for example, you send us an inquiry or press release ; register on the website; post information to public areas of the site or apply for a promotion.

By providing any/all personal information to us, you understand and clearly consent to the transfer of such information to, and the collection and processing and posting of such information in, other countries or territories. Personal data such as e-mail address, telephone numbers will be kept private and not be publicly posted, unless otherwise authorized. Comments and posts in our blog will be used as public domain.

**Cookies & Tracking**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. The third-party advertising technology that we use on this Web site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. In addition, we use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site and to deliver more relevant advertising. To “opt-out,” please visit:  
http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx.

We embed Facebook Comments plugin to allow you to leave comment at our website using your Facebook account. This plugin may collect your IP address, your web browser User Agent, store and retrieve cookies on your browser, embed additional tracking, and monitor your interaction with the commenting interface, including correlating your Facebook account with whatever action you take within the interface (such as “liking” someone’s comment, replying to other comments), if you are logged into Facebook. For more information about how this data may be used, please see Facebook’s data privacy policy: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update

**Use of Information**

We will use information collected from you in the following ways:

Marketing purposes. We may use information provided by you or our tracking services for internal marketing purposes.

Third party offers. If you opt-in, we may allow third parties to contact you with information that may interest you.

Public Areas of the Site. It is understood that if you post a comment or blog entry in our public areas (such as the blog, message board or comment area) that your entry is to be used by Shockya.com as public domain to be viewed or printed however we feel necessary, please do not submit material that you don’t want in print. These entries can be read by publicly and in any country, so we suggest to refrain from posting personal information such as e-mail addresses.

Sale and Transfer of information. In the event of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, reorganization or liquidation, we may transfer, sell, or assign to third party buyers all information concerning your relationship with us, including without limitation, personally identifiable information that you provide to us.

Administration and Data Management. We may transfer your personal information to third parties under confidentiality obligations when the performance of any service in relation to the activities above is sub-contracted (e.g. the administration of a marketing campaign).

Legal purposes. We may disclose your personal information if permitted by law or required to do so by law.

Links. This site may contain links or references to other web based sites outside of Shockya’s control. Our privacy statement does not apply on these third party sites.

Doubleclick. This website may utilize certain services provided by DoubleClick, Inc. (“DoubleClick”). For further information concerning DoubleClick’s privacy practices, including the ability to opt-out from any data collection, reporting and/or targeting activities associated with its services, please go to http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

Please visit <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> for more info.

We may need to update this privacy statement from time to time. We recommend that you regularly check this page to ensure that you have read the most recent version.

© 2007-2017 Shockya.com, California. All rights reserved.
